这是为初学者准备的 JavaScript 教程，相信你会需要它
我是 Beau Carnes，是 freeCodeCamp 的老师
在这套 JavaScript 教程中，你会学习到
入门 JavaScript 所需的全部知识点
这套课程对初学者非常友好
已经掌握 JavaScript 的人们也可以用它来回顾基础语法
这套教程和 freeCodeCamp.org 的 JavaScript 课程节奏一致
所以如果你想在学习这套教程的每个部分的时候
同时做一些在线编程挑战
你可以看一下教程中列出的 freeCodeCamp.org 相应挑战的链接
不过这套视频教程是完全独立的
所以你不一定要边看视频边做 freeCodeCamp.org 的挑战
但是边看边做是有帮助的
并且在你学习教程之后
你会想完成或者开发一些 JavaScript 项目
所以我在视频中加入了项目链接
那么学习这个视频之后你可能想要自己开发一些项目
你确实应该这样学习 JavaScript
不完全依赖教程
and just use a search engine to find the
而是使用搜索引擎来寻找你不知道的东西或者需要学习的东西
learn to go along with the free code
配合 freeCodeCamp 的课程体系
camp curriculum I have all the es6 stuff
我也会在本教程的第二部分讲到 es6 的知识点
that's pretty much it
先讲这么多
我们开始学习吧
so how exactly do you install JavaScript
怎么安装 JavaScript 呢
其实可以不用安装
几乎所有 Web 浏览器都可以运行 JavaScript
这非常棒
因为许多设备上面都有 Web 浏览器
所以当你用 JavaScript 写程序的时候
各种设备和操作系统都可以运行这个程序
所以写 JavaScript 程序是挺方便的
show you a few things you can do to
下面我来介绍一些你可以在学习本教程时用到的工具
follow along with this course you could
download a code editor here I have
sublime text you could also use Visual
Studio code or atom or any code editor
and I've created an HTML file because
HTML files can be open in web browsers
and I have these script tags these are
HTML tags but within our script tags we
have our JavaScript so if I open up this
file in a web browser it looks like this
well I can open up my JavaScript console
and then in the console you can see it
says hello world that's right from my
JavaScript program so whenever you
console that log is gonna show in the
console here you could also just use the
code editor that's included on free code
camp org like I mentioned this course
follows along with the JavaScript